行尸走肉
第十一季  第二集
锈住了
It's rusted shut.
其他门肯定也一样
Safe bet that they all are.
玛姬呢
Where's Maggie?
她刚才就在我后面
She w-- She was right behind me.
谁来托我上去
Somebody boost me up.
你上去就死定了
You go up there, you're dead.
你去的话她会生气的
She'd be pissed if you tried.
她想让我们继续前进
She'd want us to keep moving forward.
好了  我们得把那扇门打开
Alright, we need to get that door open.
然后我们穿过车厢
Then we'll go from car to car
一直走到车头
until we hit the front of the train.
然后下车
Then we'll hop off.
继续前进
And then we just keep going.
小心  伙计们
Look out, guys.
无家可归老兵
你好
没有人能够幸免
真相也是谎言
你人生的王冠
没有家
没有工作
饥饿
你知道这意味着什么  对吗
You know what this means, don't you?
那个照片板
The photo board?
联邦是真实存在的
The Commonwealth is real.
那是一张你的照片  钱包大小
That was a wallet-sized photo of you,
也就是说是放在你兄弟钱包里的
which means it was in your brother's wallet,
也就是说末世之中  他一直随身带着它
which means he kept the wallet on him in the apocalypse,
可能有十多年了  谁会这样做
possibly for 10-plus years, and who does that?
他听起来真棒
He sounds awesome.
什么
What?
你说得也对
And also what you said.
计划是什么
So what's the plan?
他们有组织架构  法律
They have structure. Laws.
有人主管这里
Someone here's in charge,
我要和那个人谈谈
and I'm going to speak to that person.
就这样吗  计划是谈谈吗
That's it? The plan is talking?
是的  冷静如冰  要求结果
Yes. Cold as ice. Demand results.
怎么了
What?
没什么  只是
Nothing. It's just...
那是你兄弟  你确定可以冷静如冰吗
it's your bro. You sure you can be "Cold as ice"?
是的  我以前是律师  本就如此
Yeah, I was a lawyer. It comes naturally.
听着  我爱我兄弟
Look, I love my brother.
但在这一切之前
But I hadn't seen him in a really long time
我已经很久没见过他了  我以为...
before all of this, and I assumed --
没关系  我可以的
It doesn't matter. I'll be fine
-只要我能和那个人...  -嘘  等会
as long as I can speak to the --Shh! Hang on.
是昨晚的那个女的
That was her, from last night.
你看到她看我们的样子了吗  她知道了
Did you see how she was looking at us? She knows.
我们没事  没人知道我们试过逃走
We're fine. No one knows we tried to leave,
相信我  不然我们会被带走的...
or believe me, we'd be called int--
以西结不见了
Ezekiel's gone.
回答你们的下一个问题
In anticipation of your next question,
我把所有地方都找过了  也问过了
I looked everywhere, asked around.
没人告诉我任何消息  有人带走他了
No one's saying anything. Someone took him.
有人知道我们做了什么
Someone knows what we did,
他是倒下的第一块多米诺骨牌
and he's just the first domino to fall.
继续回答你们后面的疑问
In anticipation of your follow-up query,
我不知道自己是怎么知道的
I don't know how I know.
我只知道我要崩溃了
I only know that I'm freaking out!
可能是因为他骂了那个大个子
It's probably 'cause he told off the big guy.
上帝  他为什么要骂他
Oh, God. Why'd he tell off the big guy?
我们应该跟他们谈谈  跟他们谈谈
We should talk to them. We should talk to them.
我们可以坦白我们是谁  从哪来
We can come clean about who we are and where we're really from.
尤金  我再说最后一遍
Eugene, for the last time,
不要跟他们的执法人员谈
do not talk to their law enforcement.
如果你别无选择
Or if you find yourself in a situation
必须开口  就坚持原来的说辞
where you have to, you stick to the story.
那我们该怎么做
Well, what do we do?
等等  你干什么  冷静
Wait, what? Be cool.
冷静如冰  如冰
Ice! Ice!
你们带走了我们的一个人吗
You've got one of our people?
你们对他做了什么
What have you done with him?
我要求知道他被带去哪里了
I demand to know where he's been taken!
女士  冷静
Ma'am, calm down.
我不知道你的朋友在哪里
I don't know where your friend is.
那我们没有必要继续对话了
Then there's no reason for us to continue this conversation.
我要和能回答我的人说话
I'd like to speak to somebody who can actually give me answers.
你向谁汇报
Who do you report to?
你想跟我的主管谈谈吗
You wanna speak to my supervisor?
没错  把你们经理叫来
That's right! We wanna talk to the manager!
亲爱的爸爸
你总是说
如果你一周没回来
我们就继续生活
妈妈没听你的话
她去找你了
已经过去三周了
所以我们也要去了
我会照顾杰西
每天十点打开无线电
希望尽快见到你们
爱你们的
汤姆和杰西
恶魔
狗  回来  回来
Hey, Dog! Come here! Come here!
狗
Hey! Dog!
回来
Come here!
狗
Dog!
我不知道你为什么来这里
I'm not sure why you're here.
你已经被评估过了
You've already been assessed.
你以为你们在评估我吗
You think you've been assessing me?
不  亲爱的
No, dear.
是我在评估你们
I've been assessing you.
你对我一无所知
You don't know anything about me --
你们的社区庞大又有组织
Your community's large and organized.
你们有官僚机构  你们是其中的成员
There's a bureaucracy, and you're part of it.
也许在灾变之前  你做的也是类似的工作
You probably had a job like this before the world fell.
要我猜  我会说
If I had to guess, I'd say
你曾是法证心理学家
forensic psychologist.
也许你以前是学者
Perhaps you were an academic.
研究员
Researcher?
你们的职责是为社区评估威胁
Your role is to assess threat for your community.
你们问我们过去的身份
You ask about who we were
因为你们的上级认为
because someone above you has decided
那是不错的基准线
that that's a good baseline position
能评判现在的我们
from which to judge who we are.
所以你们在我们大脑尘封的记忆中搜索
So you poke around the dusty corners of our brains,
询问我们的如厕习惯
test our sense of boundaries
来测试我们的边界感
with queries about our toileting habits.
因为一张两元钞票  你们狠狠训斥了我的人
You raked one of my people over the coals due to a $2 bill,
这让我认为你们的流通货币是美元
which makes me believe your currency is the U.S. Dollar,
你们需要严格管控现钞的数量
and that you need to strictly control the amount in circulation.
你们使用熟悉的钱  作为一种强大的心理策略
You use familiar money as a powerful psychological tactic,
因为你们知道人们有多怀念过去的世界
because you know how desperately people miss the old world.
你们想了解我们的能耐
You want to understand what we're capable of
了解我们是能帮助你们的社区变大变强
and whether we can enhance your community
还是只会白白浪费资源
or if we'd simply be a drain on resources.
但真相是  你们也要证明自己存在的合理性
But the truth of it is, you need to justify your existence, too.
因为如今一个能运走垃圾
Because isn't it almost more valuable now
让街道远离疾病的人
to have someone who can haul the trash
难道不比一个
and keep the streets free from disease
能写下无尽问题清单的人更有价值吗
than someone who can write endless lists of questions,
毕竟到头来
given that at the end of the day,
你只能靠直觉来判断
you just need to rely on your gut instinct
坐在你对面的人
about whether or not the person across from you
是否会在你入睡时杀了你
will or won't murder you in your sleep?
但你们都是循规蹈矩的人
But you're both people that follow the rules.
我曾是律师
I was a lawyer.
我喜欢规矩
I like rules.
这能给混乱带来秩序
They bring order to the chaos.
这意味着你们需要我
Which means you need me.
我有理由相信我的兄弟  一名胸外科医生
I have reason to believe my brother, a thoracic surgeon,
就住在联邦  他正在找我
is living at the Commonwealth and is looking for me.
我希望我的团队获得加急评估
I'd like expedited processing for my group,
依据你们社区的庇护和移民政策
as per your community's asylum and immigration policies.
你在哪里上的学来着
Where did you go to school again?
牛津大学念的本科  在哈佛念的法学博士
Undergraduate at Oxford, JD is from Harvard,
你已经很清楚了
which you very well know.
你想让我再列出我的职业资格证书吗
Would you like me to list my professional credentials again?
喝咖啡吗
Coffee?
你能别动了吗  你让我的
Can you stop moving? You're taking my nerves over the edge
焦虑指数爆表了
to a proverbial 11 on a scale of 10.
我控制不了  我们一直在等
I can't help it. We've been waiting and waiting,
现在我真的好想解手
and now I have to pee really, really bad.
我不该提的  我马上回来
I shouldn't have mentioned it. Be right back.
不  别分开了
No! No! No more splitting up!
尤金  既然那个穿着橙色服装的帅哥
Eugene. If that fine-ass dude in the orange suit
刚送了一杯咖啡进去
just walked in with a coffee,
那由美子的情况肯定很好  对吧
things must be going good for Yumiko, right?
也许我回来时她就出来了
Maybe she'll be out by the time I'm back.
打扰了[以下为西语]
有什么能帮你的
我能去外面解手的那个洞吗
你可以去这里的洗手间
什么洗手间  这里有洗手间吗
进去  右拐
好...
有卫生纸吗
Uh, do you have toilet paper?
该死
Well, shit!
我好激动
I'm excited!
听我数  三二一
On my count. 3, 2, 1!
你们去解决那个吧
Why don't you guys handle that one?
如果你们累了  我们就接手
If you get tired out, we'll take over.
是顶上传来的声音吗
Is that the roof?
可能是行尸
Could be walkers.
声音是下面传来的  是摩斯电码
It's below us. It's Morse code.
意思是救命
It's SOS.
我滑倒了
I slipped.
他看见了  却留下我等死
He saw, and he left me to die.
嗯
Yeah.
好吧  那又如何
Okay. So what?
你就直接承认了吗
You're just admitting it?
你想杀了她
You tried to kill her!
不  她有麻烦了  我没帮忙
No, she was in trouble, and I didn't help.
这两者区别很大
There is a big difference.
好吧  现在谁会帮你
Okay, so who's gonna help you now?
这里有谁会支持你
Who in here's got your back?
不用手指也能数出那个数
Yeah, you don't need fingers to count that number.
她刚还在说要杀了我
She was just talking about murdering me,
宜早不宜迟
sooner rather than later,
但是我却成了混蛋
and yet somehow, I'm the big, old asshole
就因为我没有为她冒生命危险吗
'cause I didn't risk my nuts for her?
我为你们每个人
I have been a golden goddamn asset
都提供了巨大的帮助
for every single one of you.
是啊  烧掉山顶寨也有帮助  对吧
Yeah, burning Hilltop, that helped, huh?
我杀了阿尔法  对吧
I killed Alpha, right?
所以没错  是有帮助
So, yeah, I was helpful.
因为如果我没那样做
'Cause if I hadn't done that,
你认识的所有人  头颅都会被钉在柱子上
every person you know, their skull would be on a spike.
我做了必须做的事  好吗
I did what needed to be done, alright?
我有在努力
I am trying.
好吧  我一个字也不信
Yeah, okay. I'm not buying a word of it.
我也是
Same.
点点头  我就动手
Nod and it happens.
没有他  我们也能穿过城市
We can get through the city without him.
救命  救救我
Help! Help me! Help!
-回头再说  -救命
- Later. - Help!
救命
Help!
盖奇  发生了什么
Gage?! What happened?!
我们在隧道里迷路了  到处都是行尸
We got lost in the tunnels! Walkers are everywhere,
-它们也许...  -你怎么进去的
- they -- they might have -- - How'd you get in there?
我打开了远端的一扇门
I-I got a door open on the far end.
你关了门吗
Did you close it?
-盖奇  -我...
- Gage? - I --
这玩意儿似乎松动了  大脚怪  帮帮忙
Hey, this one seems a bit looser. Sasquatch, gimme a hand.
我们要是开门  行尸会一拥而入
We open that, they'll all get in.
他就在我们眼前
He's right there!
我知道
I know he is.
去你的
The hell with you.
奥尔登
Alden?
快啊
Come on.
你疯了吗  让开
Are you insane? Move!
让开
Move!
玛姬
Maggie?
Maggie?!
开门
Open the door!
我很抱歉  好吗  对不起
Look, I'm sorry, okay?! I'm sorry --
我犯了个错  对不起
I made -- I made a mistake, and I'm sorry,
但我只是
but I just --
再给我一次机会  好吗
I want another chance. Okay?
我不会再这样做了
I won't do it again. I won't do it again.
我会表现更好  求你了
I'll do better. Please, I -- Please.
玛姬  听我说
Maggie, listen to me.
我们有时间  我们可以打开那扇门
We have time. We can get that door open.
玛姬  玛姬
Maggie! Maggie!
我们没有足够的弹药杀掉它们
We don't have the ammo to clear them.
放手吧
Let it go.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不能开门
I can't.
骗子
Liar.
打扰了  我在等我的朋友  由美子
Pardon me. I've been waiting for my friend, Yumiko.
她就在那个房间里
She's in that room right there.
请问你能否告知我
I was wondering if you might be able to provide
她何时才能出来
or procure for me an ETA for when she might be done?
里面没人
No one's in there.
但我看着我的朋友和两个提问人进去了
But I watched my friend walk in there with the two questioners,
我没见到她或他们走出来
and I haven't seen her or them walk out.
如果你可以去看看
If you could just check --
里面没人  先生
No one is in there, sir.
我的另一个朋友去女厕所了
My other friend went to use the ladies' room --
什么朋友
What friend?
我得请你离开了
I need you to leave.
立刻
Now.
怎么了
What is it?
糟糕的回忆
Bad memories.
什么回忆
Of what?
你们不愿意看他
You guys don't wanna look at him.
为什么
Why?
你们为什么不看他
Why won't you look at him?
那不过是一副空皮囊  他死得像个懦夫
All that is, is the shell of a man who died a coward.
真会说啊  神父
That's a hot take, Father.
他确实是怕了
He was scared,
但他不该那样死去
but he didn't deserve to die like that.
那是最糟糕的死法
In the worst way imaginable.
有更糟糕的死法
There are worse ways.
糟糕得多
A lot worse.
在我找到伊莱哲和他的人之前
Before I found Elijah and his people...
赫谢尔和我单独生活了很久
Hershel and I were alone for a long time.
有一天  我们碰到了一个虚弱的老人
One day, we came across this frail old man
他跪在一个翻倒的超市购物车旁边
who was kneeling by a turned-over grocery cart.
里面全是找来的衣服
It was full of scavenged clothes
他说是给他的儿女们穿的
he said were for his sons and daughters,
问我们能否帮他把车拉回去
and could we help him haul the cart back home?
他说他会给我们食物来补偿
And he said he'd give us food for our trouble.
我知道他是个骗子
I knew that he was a liar.
但我很饿
But I was starving,
不久后  赫谢尔也会挨饿
and soon, Hershel would be.
所以我们跟着他去了他家
So we followed him back to his house.
我用刀抵着他的脖子  搜了他的口袋
I held a knife to his throat and reached in his pocket.
我掏出了他原本用来迷晕我的氯仿布
I pulled out the chloroform rag he was gonna use on me.
塞在了他的嘴里
I stuffed it in his mouth.
然后我们进了房子
And then we went inside the house,
我把儿子锁在一个房间里
and I locked my little boy in a room,
然后去探索房子
and I went and searched the house.
那里有三个
There were these three...
畸形的
deformed --
我都不会称他们为人
I wouldn't call them men.
他们冲着我来了
They came after me.
但我解决了他们
But I handled them.
然后整个房子都安静了
And then the house was quiet,
只剩下楼上
except for this thudding sound
阁楼里传来的砰砰声
that was coming from upstairs in the attic.
我以为楼上有人被绑了
And I thought maybe they had people tied up up there
他们想逃跑
that were trying to get free.
所以我走到走廊尽头的一扇门前
So I walked to a door at the end of this hallway.
我打开门  抬头看
And I opened it, and I looked up,
那里有一排楼梯
and there was a set of stairs.
在楼梯顶部有个影子
At the top of the stairs, there's this shadow
在扭动和摇摆
writhing and rocking.
我以为是个动物
I thought it was an animal.
突然间  它从楼梯上掉了下来
Then all of a sudden, it fell down the stairs,
落在了我的脚边
and it came right at my feet.
那是个行尸
It was a walker
曾经是个女人
that used to be a woman.
她的胳膊和腿
Her arms and her legs
都被砍掉了
had been cut off,
缝合了伤口
stitched up.
她的眼睛被挖掉了
Her eyes gouged out.
没有舌头
No tongue.
她在呼呼喘息
And she was wheezing
透过喉咙上敞开的  被灼烧过的伤口
through an open, cauterized gash in her throat
她的声带被扯掉了
where her vocal cords had been ripped out.
她的肚子又大又圆
And her belly was round and full.
里面的那个东西想要破肚而出
And whatever was inside of there was trying to get out.
我走上楼  楼上有三个像她一样的人
And I went upstairs, and there were three more just like her.
但她们依然有心跳
But their hearts were still beating.
你知道我当时的第一个想法是什么吗
And do you know the first thing I thought?
我所想到的第一件事是什么吗
The very first thing that crossed my mind?
"既然她们活着
"If they're alive,
那这里一定有食物"
there must be food here."
所以我解决了她们
So I took care of them.
然后找到了食物
And then I found the food.
非常多的食物
Lots of it.
赫谢尔和我装满了购物车  然后走了
And Hershel and I filled the cart with it, and we left.
在告诉你这件事时  我没有任何情绪
I don't feel anything when I tell you that.
你懂我的意思吗
Do you understand me?
因为外面就是这样的世界
Because that is what's out there.
看到那一幕  让我失去了某些东西
And seeing it, I lost something.
而我认为失去那些东西不是件坏事
And I don't think it's a bad thing that I did.
因为这让一切变得清晰多了
Because it has made things so much clearer.
我们在亚历山大
What we have in Alexandria,
在山顶寨和子午镇
what we had in Hilltop
所拥有的一切
and in Meridian --
非常稀有
it's rare.
一定如此
It has to be.
与外面的一切相比起来
Compared to everything that's out there.
因为如果不是的话...
Because if it isn't --
这意味着我们很走运
It means we were lucky.
这意味着没人搞清楚了该做什么
It means that nobody has it figured out.
以前没人搞清楚
Nobody ever did,
以后也不会有人搞清楚
and nobody ever will.
狗
Dog?
达里尔  救救我
Daryl, help me.
有多严重
How bad is it?
不乐观
It ain't good.
你去上面了吗
You went topside?
嗯
Yeah.
坏主意
Bad idea.
我和盖奇走散了
I lost Gage.
弹药包呢
Where's the ammo bag?
我也弄丢了
I lost that, too.
别  住手
Don't -- Stop.
别浪费在我身上
Don't waste that on me.
给  我只有这些了
Here. It's all I got.
告诉我的孩子们  我没有像懦夫一样死去
Tell my kids I didn't die a coward.
卡住了
It's blocked.
它们从这边来了
They're coming in from this side!
退后
Back up!
嘘  小子
Shh, boy.
快  再挪开点
Come on, little more!
快点
Hurry!
快走
Come on, go!
找掩护
Get behind something!
你们把我的旅伴们怎么了
What have you done with my traveling companions?
他们正在被评估处理
They're being processed.
是指行政上的"评估"
"Processed" as in a-administratively?
还是像红肠或其他肉一样被"处理"了
"Processed" as in bologna or other meat stuffs?
我的好奇心需要得到答案
This inquiring mind needs to know.
我要见他们
I want to see them.
你喜欢紧张吗
You like feeling nervous?
不喜欢
No.
只有一件事能让我紧张起来
Only one thing gets my heart up.
当我在外面
When I'm out there,
与死尸战斗时
battling the dead.
心潮澎湃
The magenta swarms.
真是...
It's just...
每一次都血脉偾张
pumping, every time.
但这不是坏事
But not in a bad way.
给  擦干净
Here. Mop up.
-我认为...  -你屁谎都不会说
I-I think that -- You can't lie for shit.
-我...   -所以别说了
I -- So don't lie.
好  我没打算说谎
Okay. I wasn't g-going to.
没打算啊
You weren't?
嗯
No.
那我对你有好感了
That makes me like you.
继续保持下去  能帮到你自己
Keep doing that, it'll help you.
如果你不这样...
If you don't --
你懂吧
You get me?
大声说出来
Use your words.
懂  我懂  长官
Y-Yes. Yes, sir.
很好
Good.
现在
Now.
我知道你有所隐瞒
I know you're holding back.
你知道你有所隐瞒
You know you're holding back.
我会问你两个问题
I'm going to give you two questions.
你要给我两个回答  真实的回答
You're going to give me two answers. Truthful ones.
做到这点
You do that?
你就能走
You get to go.
你就能再次见到你的朋友们
You get to see your friends again.
一切都会好起来
Everything will be okay.
就这么简单
It's that simple.
准备好了吗
Ready?
你们的社区在哪里
Where is your settlement?
你们为什么去那个火车站
And why were you at that train station?
尤金
Mm, Eugene.
如果你说谎
If you lie.
我会知道的
I'll know.
好的
O-Okey-dokey.
你说得对
You're right.
我的确隐瞒了一些事
I have been holding something back.
实话说  我之前就想说出来
Frankly, I wanted to speak up before this,
但我担心我的朋友们会不满
but I was afraid of what my friends would think.
我以前不是个感情外露的人
I haven't always been the most emotional fella,
但一万小时以上的死亡  失去和恐惧
but my 10,000-plus hours of death, loss, and fear
让我敞开了一点心扉
have opened me up a little bit.
在我们的旅途中  我发现了一台无线电
In the course of our travels, I found this radio.
每天晚上  我都对着虚空说话
Night after night, I would speak into the void,
期待着"假如"发生
holding onto a-a "what if,"
这是愚人的做法  而我只是个愚人
as fools are wont to do, and I am nothing if not a fool.
然后一天晚上
Then one night,
虚空中传回了一个声音
a voice came back from said void.
一个动听的声音
A beautiful voice.
我们聊了起来  而她...
We got to talking, and she...
不反感我的想法
...was not repulsed by my musings.
我们聊到了火车博物馆和冰淇淋甜筒
We spoke of train museums and ice cream cones.
我们欢笑
We laughed.
我们唱了铁娘子乐队的歌
We sang Iron Maiden.
然后我们想见面
And then we wanted to meet.
所以我叫上了朋友们
So I got my friends
去了那个火车场  假装可以
to go to that train yard under the guise
求出现在那里的人帮助我们三人
of asking whoever showed up for help for us three,
因为我知道不然他们是不会去的
because I knew they wouldn't go otherwise.
但我的脑子里只有史蒂芬妮
But all I was thinking about was Stephanie.
所以没错  我说谎了
So yes, I lied.
我一直在说谎  因为我害怕失去
I've been lying this whole time, because I'm afraid to lose
我在这世界上仅剩的三个朋友
the three friends I have in this world.
我骗史蒂芬妮说我来自一个大社区
And I lied to Stephanie about being from a large settlement
因为我害怕也许
because I was afraid that maybe,
她不是她所说的那个人
she was not who she said she was.
也许这是个美人计
That maybe she was a femme fatale,
专给孤独之人下套
laying a trap for a lonely heart.
我在恋爱方面向来一塌糊涂
My track record in the romantic realm is spotty at best.
我与任何人都搞不好关系
I'm not one for whom any relationships come easy,
尤其是与异性佳人
particularly those with the fairer sex.
我其实还是个处男
And I am, in fact, a virgin.
尽管我曾多次观察过房事
Even though I have, uh, observed the act
次数多到我都不好意思承认了
far more times than I care to admit.
感谢你们忍住了嘲笑
Thank you for holding back your titters.
我本希望
I was -- I was hoping
在经过适度追求后
that after a suitable period of courtship,
史蒂芬妮也许能改变我这难堪的状态
that Stephanie might be the one to change my unenviable status,
因为我在内心深处希望
because deep down, I was hoping that maybe, in fact,
她是我的一生真爱
she was my One True Love.
现在我被迫在这个房间里承认了这件事
And now I've been forced to admit that in this room,
这让我羞耻万分
and I'm humiliated by it.
而且
And...
我害怕如果史蒂芬妮知道了
I'm afraid that if Stephanie finds out
我没对她说实话
that I wasn't honest with her, either,
她就永远不理我了
that she might want to have nothing to do with me anymore.
所以我在这里
So here I am...
坦白了这件事  长舒了一口气
very relieved to get that off my chest.
因为除此之外  我至今为止说的每句话
Because everything else I've said up to this point
都他妈的是真话
has been the goddamn truth.
尤金
Eugene!
没事了  哥们  哭出来
It's okay, man. Let it out.
我以为...  他们带你们去了哪里
I thought -- W-Where'd they take you?
一个医务室
An infirmary.
有个医生给我做了雾疗  给了我难喝的草药止咳糖浆
A medic steamed my face, gave me this nasty herbal cough syrup,
然后我睡着了
and I slept.
他们在糖浆里下药了吗
They spiked the cough syrup?
不是  他们麻醉了我
No, no. They took the lantern out of my room,
我入睡了
and I fell asleep.
医生检查了我几次
Medic checked on me a couple of times,
然后他们带由美子来看了我
and then they brought Yumiko to visit,
然后带我们去等待室见了公主
and then they took us to a holding room with Princess,
然后带我们来了这里
and then they brought us here.
对  谢天谢地你也来了  我们很担心你
Yeah. Thank God you're here, too. We were worried.
根据《新永久联合条例》第114A节
Pursuant to Section 114A of the New Articles of Perpetual Union,
遵从《原宪法》第1条第8节
in deference to traditions established by Article 1,
《原世界人权宣言》第14条
Section 8 of the Legacy Constitution
所确立的传统
and Article 14 of the Legacy UDHR,
你们已成功通过了在此联合城镇
you have successfully completed initial processing
获得庇护和公民权的初步评估
in consideration for asylum and citizenship in these united townships.
在你们穿过这些门后
When you walk through these doors,
将有"片警"护送你们
you'll be escorted to orientation.
去参加迎新
By a beat cop.
欢迎来到联邦
Welcome to the Commonwealth.
我上的是西点军校  混蛋
I went to West Point, asshole.
我不懂  有什么变了  他们为什么突然...
I don't get it. What the hell changed? Why did they all --
别质疑了  我们进去了
Don't question it. We're in.
你们哪位是尤金
Which one of you is Eugene?
我是史蒂芬妮
I'm Stephanie.
迪加德东市场站
那是什么
What is that?
一个孩子给他父母写的信
It's a letter from this kid to his parents.
过去的东西
It's from back before.
你找到的吗
You found it?
嗯  在隧道里
Yeah, down in the tunnels.
在下面看到别的东西了吗
See anything else down there?
没有  跟你看到的一样
Nah. Just the same stuff you saw.
我们出发吗
We heading out?
我们得先绕个路
We need to take a detour first.
阿伯山
Arbor Hills.
-那里有什么  -隐藏的补给站
- What's there? - Hidden supply depot.
乔吉在很多地方都设了  以防我们外出
Georgie set 'em up all over, in case we ran into any trouble
寻找幸存者时遇到麻烦
when we were out looking for survivors.
那里有弹药  食物  武器
It has ammo, food, weapons.
我们在那里休息  补充资源  然后去子午镇
Rest up there, restock, and then head to Meridian.
那附近的地标是个无线电塔
Radio tower marks that neighborhood.
你知道在哪里吗
You know where that is?
知道  来吧
Yeah. Come on.
走吧  小子
Come on. Come on, boy.
这地方跟我上次来相比
Well, this place sure has gone to shit
真是变得糟透了
since the last time I was here.
我们原路回去  可以抄小道...
Let's double back. We can cut through --